e-naira.com 2007-12-08

# Nigerian Online Payment Solution Provider

NIGERIAN ONLINE PAYMENT SOLUTION PROVIDER

PRIVACY POLICY

**E-naira.com is committed to a proactive, pro-user Privacy Policy. Your privacy is extremely important to us.  

INTRODUCTION  
This privacy statement describes privacy aspects specific to the e-naira.com web site. We respect and actively protect the privacy of those who visit and use e-naira.com. To demonstrate our integrity and commitment to fair information practices, we have adopted leading industry privacy guidelines. 

1\. CONFIDENTIALITY  
e-naira.com does not share, sell, lease, loan, rent, trade or disclose any personal information collected in the use of this Site or the creation of your VISA Card Account.

2\. PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION  
e-naira.com collects no personally identifying information about you except when you knowingly and specifically submit this information for a special purpose.

3\. E-MAIL LISTS  
e-naira.com may maintain e-mail lists and newsletters to enlighten and inform our users, clients and the media about our services, and/or announce upcoming news and special events.

**

**4\. MINORS  
Because of the financial nature of our business, this Site is not designed to appeal to children under 18 years of age. e-naira.com does not knowingly attempt to solicit or receive any information from minors and children; and they are prohibited from using our Site and Services**.

**5\. CHANGES TO THIS POLICY  
Any changes or updates to this privacy statement will be effective immediately upon posting to this site before they take effect.Your continued use of this Web site will demonstrate your acceptance of the terms specified by this Privacy Policy.**

**6\. YOUR CONSENT  
Except where we may be legally required to disclose certain information to comply with a legal process; no information relating to your use of this Site will be disclosed to an outside party without your express consent.**

**7\. CONTACTING US  
Additional questions or concerns regarding the privacy practices of e-naira.com should be addressed to privacy@e-naira.com **
